[
  {
    "question": "5 + 7 = ?",
    "options": [
      "10",
      "11",
      "12",
      "13"
    ],
    "answer": "12"
  }
  ,
  {
    "question": "12 - 8 = ?",
    "options": [
      "1",
      "2",
      "3",
      "4"
    ],
    "answer": "4"
  }
  ,
  {
    "question": "4 * 8 = ?",
    "options": [
      "31",
      "23",
      "39",
      "32"
    ],
    "answer": "32"
  }
  ,
  {
    "question": "16 / 8 = ?",
    "options": [
      "1",
      "2",
      "3",
      "4"
    ],
    "answer": "2"
  }
  ,
  {
    "question": "1 + 8 = ?",
    "options": [
      "1",
      "2",
      "3",
      "9"
    ],
    "answer": "9"
  }
  ,
  {
    "question": "12 % 8 = ?",
    "options": [
      "1",
      "2",
      "3",
      "4"
    ],
    "answer": "4"
  }
  ,
  {
    "question": "12 - 8 = ?",
    "options": [
      "1",
      "2",
      "3",
      "4"
    ],
    "answer": "4"
  }
  ,
  {
    "question": "4 - 3 = ?",
    "options": [
      "1",
      "2",
      "3",
      "4"
    ],
    "answer": "1"
  }
  ,
  {
    "question": "12 * 8 - 6 = ?",
    "options": [
      "91",
      "92",
      "93",
      "90"
    ],
    "answer": "4"
  }
  ,
  {
    "question": "12 % 9 = ?",
    "options": [
      "1",
      "2",
      "3",
      "4"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  }

]